[
    {
        "question":"bear",
        "answer":"熊"
    },
    {
        "question":"bird",
        "answer":"鳥"
    },
    {
        "question":"elephant",
        "answer": "大象"
    },
    {
        "question":"penguin",
        "answer": "企鵝"
    },
    {
        "question":"crocodile",
        "answer": "鱷魚"
    },
    {
        "question":"jellyfish",
        "answer": "水母"
    },
    {
        "question":"donkey",
        "answer": "毛驢"
    },
    {
        "question":"zebra",
        "answer": "斑馬"
    },
    {
        "question":"horse",
        "answer": "馬"
    },
    {
        "question":"monkey",
        "answer": "猴子"
    },
    {
        "question":"sloth",
        "answer": "樹懶"
    },
    {
        "question":"eagle",
        "answer": "飛鷹"
    },
    {
        "question":"beaver",
        "answer": "河狸"
    },
    {
        "question":"dinosaur",
        "answer": "恐龍"
    },
    {
        "question":"snake",
        "answer": "蛇"
    },
    {
        "question":"dog",
        "answer": "狗"
    },
    {
        "question":"cat",
        "answer": "貓"
    },
    {
        "question":"tiger",
        "answer": "老虎"
    },
    {
        "question":"lion",
        "answer": "獅子"
    },
    {
        "question":"parrot",
        "answer": "鸚鵡"
    },
    {
        "question":"bee",
        "answer": "蜜蜂"
    },
    {
        "question":"ant",
        "answer": "螞蟻"
    },
    {
        "question":"lizard",
        "answer": "蜥蜴"
    },
    {
        "question":"pig",
        "answer": "豬"
    },
    {
        "question":"sheep",
        "answer": "羊"
    },
    {
        "question":"goat",
        "answer": "山羊"
    },
    {
        "question":"fish",
        "answer": "魚"
    },
    {
        "question":"shark",
        "answer": "鯊魚"
    },
    {
        "question":"mouse",
        "answer": "老鼠"
    },
    {
        "question":"spider",
        "answer": "蜘蛛"
    },
    {
        "question":"cockroach",
        "answer": "蟑螂"
    },
    {
        "question":"turtle",
        "answer": "烏龜"
    },
    {
        "question":"giraffe",
        "answer": "長頸鹿"
    },
    {
        "question":"worm",
        "answer": "蟲子"
    },
    {
        "question":"deer",
        "answer": "鹿"
    },
    {
        "question":"snail",
        "answer": "蝸牛"
    }
]